=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=
HOW TO GET THE COMPLETE PUMA 2020/2021 FONT
=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=

The Puma 2020/2021 font is a donationware font, meaning that you are 
required to make a donation before you will receive the Puma 2020/2021 
font. I will leave it up for you to decide how much to donate but 
please be generous. 

The font is both in TTF and OTF formats. The font contains basic letters 
and numbers, a period, a hyphen and a wide range of accented letters. 
The font has 258 glyphs which includes  A B C D E F G H I J K L M N O P 
Q R S T U V W X Y Z . 0 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 0 - À Á Â Ã Ä Å Ā Ă Æ Ć Ĉ Ċ Č 
Ď Ð È É Ê Ë Ē Ĕ Ė Ě Ĝ Ğ Ġ Ģ Ĥ Ħ Ì Í Î Ï Ĩ Ī Ĭ İ Ĵ Ķ Ĺ Ľ Ŀ Ł Ļ Ñ Ń Ň Ņ Ŋ 
Ò Ó Ô Õ Ö Ō Ŏ Ő Ø Œ Þ Ŕ Ř Ŗ Ś Ŝ Ș Š ß Ť Ț Ŧ Ù Ú Û Ü Ũ Ū Ŭ Ů Ű Ŵ Ẁ Ẃ Ẅ Ý 
Ŷ Ÿ Ź Ż Ž.


=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=
HOW TO MAKE A DONATION
=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=

 1. Go to PayPal by using this donation link - https://bit.ly/2ESG14g

 2. Indicate the amount of donation and, as earlier mentioned, please be generous.

 3. Provide other information required by PayPal and follow instructions from PayPal.

 4. Submit the donation.

 5. Send me an email at freefootballfonts@gmail.com and let me know about 
    the donation that you just made. The font will be sent to the email 
    address used to make the PayPal donation.
 
    I give credit to those who send a donation. Let me know if you want 
    the donation to be anonymous so that your name will not be mentioned 
    on my page.
   

=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=
ADDITIONAL CONDITIONS
=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=

 + A donation for the Puma 2020/2021 font does not apply to other 
   fonts that may also require a donation. In the same way, donations for 
   other fonts will not apply as donation for the Puma 2020/2021 
   font. Donations for other fonts should be made separately.

 + Give me 24 hours, at most, to send you the font. This is to give 
   allowance for time zone differences.

 + The donation is non-refundable once the font has already been emailed 
   to the donor.

 + I reserve the right to reject a donation. Donations that are not 
   accepted will be refunded to the donor's PayPal account. This is 
   the only acceptable way of refunding a donation.

 + In case of a refund, the donor agrees to shoulder PayPal's transaction 
   fee amounting to USD 0.30 (30 US cents), which will be deducted from 
   the amount to be refunded.
  
 + By sending a donation for the Puma 2020/2021 font means that you 
   agree to all of the conditions mentioned on this page.
 
=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=